一些孩子梦想成为宇航员
Some kids dream of being astronauts.
一些孩子梦想成为棒球运动员
Some kids dream of playing baseball.
当我小的时候 我只有一个梦想
When I was a kid, I had only one dream.
就是想造一栋摩天大楼
To build a skyscraper.
那很蠢
That's stupid.
这条路是坎坷的
There were some obstacles along the way.
但是最终我的梦想实现了
But eventually my dream came true.
我成为了一名建筑师
I became an architect.
早上好  各位
Morning, everyone!
我有个设计大堂的创意
So, I had an idea for the atrium.
看好
Ready?
圆柱
Columns.
那太糟了
That's stupid.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
Transcript : Raceman Subtitles : Willow's Team
老爸老妈的浪漫史 第二季 第十三集
翻译：    jupiter1     校对：     雨亦奇
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
我不个敢相信你弄翻了我的模型
I... I can't believe you knocked over my model.
不过...它不是最新的创意 是不是  圆柱?
Well, it's just... it's not exactly new, is it-- columns?
你一下惊世骇俗的创意是什么?天花板?
I mean, what's your next groundbreaking idea-- ceilings?
地板?
Floors?
窗户?
Windows?
我知道你在想什么 这垃圾是谁?
I know what you're thinking: Who's this jerk?
这家伙是汉默・德拉泽
Well, this jerk was Hammond Druthers,
建筑界的一个传奇
a legend in the architecture community.
在80年代最牛的
Very big in the '80s.
他也是我碰到过的最最糟糕的老板
He was also far and away the worst boss I ever had.
当我设计了斯波坎国家银行大楼
Then I designed the Spokane National Bank Building.
我忽然成了他的上司
And suddenly... I was his boss.
- 并且他不喜欢我 - 楼梯?
- And he didn't like it. - Stairs?
老实讲  我也不确信我有多喜欢他
And to be honest, I wasn't sure I liked it either.
以前  当我仅仅是员工的时候
See, before, when I was just another employee,
我是快乐  无忧无虑的
I was happy, carefree.
在休息室开老板玩笑的家伙
The guy who hung out in the break room making fun of the boss.
你看他今天穿了什么?
Did you see what he was wearing today?
他的裤子穿到了胸部
It was like his pants were being held up by his nipples.
而且那件花衬衫 我看着它就会花粉过敏
Yeah, and that shirt with the flowers, I get hay fever just looking at it.
但是...突然间 我成为另外一种人了
But suddenly I was a different guy.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
有什么好笑的事情
What's so funny?
没什么
Nothing.
衬衫不错
Um... nice shirt.
谢谢
Thanks.
在公司的时间是疯狂的
The hours were insane.
我总是在不停的工作 即使不是工作时间
I was always working even when I wasn't at work.
罗宾我刚有一好主意
Oh, Robin... I just had a great idea.
无论你对我做什么 只要不吵醒我
Oh, do whatever you want to me just don't wake me up.
以前  我是这样的人
Before, I used to be this guy.
你应该请天假 去看喷火战机音乐会
Dude, of course you should take the day off for the Foo Fighters concert.
就说你病了
Just say you're sick.
但现在
But now...
我成为了这样的人
I was this guy.
病了?
Sick, huh?
把你的衬衫扣子解开
Unbutton your shirt.
喷火战机 (衣服上的字)
Hmm... "Foo Fighters."
回去工作
Get back to work.
但是德拉泽仍然最难搞定
But still, the worst part was Druthers.
-我在想... -天花板?
- Well, I was thinking... - Ceilings? Oops.
已经说过了 在说一次 你似乎喜欢重复旧的想法
Said that already. Then again, you seem to like rehashing old ideas.
当然 开玩笑的
I'm kidding, of course.
又一小鸟球 老板
Another hole in one, boss.
他一定长的很帅
Oh, wow, he must be really good-looking.
为什么你会那样说?
Why would you say that?
因为只有帅的人 才能不负责任说那样的事
Well, 'cause only good-looking people can get away with saying things like that.
我发现那是真的
I have found that to be true.
这是一种祝福  也是种诅咒
It's a blessing and a curse really.
你不能让他那样继续下去
Ted, you can't let him treat you like that.
你得问问你自己 "谁是老板" (老影片名)
Yeah, you gotta ask yourself, who's the boss?
托尼  安吉拉  莫娜 (电影中的人物)
- Tony. - Angela. - Mona.
莫娜
Mona?
仔细看看  你会改变看法的
Watch it more closely. Rock your world.
因此 你准备怎么做
So, what are you gonna do?
有的尴尬这人以前是我的上司
Well... it's awkward, I mean, the guy used to be my boss.
所以 我和主管合伙人谈了
So, I went to talk to the managing partner.
炒掉他
Fire him.
我在想他可能 被安排到别的项目上去
Well, sir, I was thinking he could just be put on a different project.
炒了他
Fire him!
他是一个自大的 过时 的人
He's an arrogant, washed-up, pain in the ass.
炒掉那个项目的所有的人
In fact, fire everyone on that project.
德拉泽 莫斯比 他们整个团队
Druthers, Mosby, the whole lot of them.
莫斯比? 我听说他做的不错
Mosby, sir? I, I... I hear Mosby's doing some great work.
莫斯比可以留下 但是告诉他 他仍处于观察期
Fine, Mosby can stay. But tell him he's on thin ice.
过来
Come here.
我喜欢你  克罗斯比
I like you, Crosby.
不介意我给手机充下电
You mind if I charge my phone?
请便
Knock yourself out.
如果你真的想炒了德拉泽 把握好时机...
Well, Ted, if you do fire Druthers, the key is timing.
还记的我不得不炒掉 我的化妆师的时候
Remember when I had to fire my makeup artist?
维基  我很抱歉
Vicki, um... I'm so sorry about this,
但是一些预算被削减了
but there's been some budget cuts and, um,
我们不得不辞掉你
we have to let you go.
我的意思是  过了今晚
I mean, after tonight.
我仍然需要化妆上台播报
I still need my makeup for the broadcast.
因此
So...
我们为受害者家属送上祝福和祈祷
Our thoughts and prayers go out to the families of the victims.
你知道吗  我将那样做
You know what? I'm gonna do it.
我明天会炒了德拉泽
I'm gonna fire Druthers tomorrow.
- 天啊 - 怎么了
- Oh, my God! - What?
- 你知道这个吗? - 不知道
- Do you know about this? - No.
那是什么
What is that?
到目前为止最伟大的事情
Only the greatest thing ever.
等等  那样还不够
Wait, wait, wait-- that's not enough buildup.
就算他们明天有医治癌症的办法
If they were to cure cancer tomorrow,
这仍然是这个星期最伟大的事情
this would still be the greatest thing to happen all week.
现在你们请看看马修的裸画
Okay. Now you're ready for naked Marshall.
天啊
Oh, my God.
简直是太棒了　太棒好几倍
This is awesome times awesome.
不对　太棒的平方
It's awesome squared.
我明白 一直在钢琴后面
I know, right? Behind the piano this whole time.
如果马修把它藏起来了
Wait. If Marshall went to all this trouble to hide it,
他显然不想我们找到他它
he clearly doesn't want us to find it.
不会吧 罗宾
Oh, come on, Robin.
我说他一定会很尴尬
No, I'm saying that he must be really embarrassed by this.
我们偷着乐好了
We are gonna have so much fun.
明白 一定很好玩
I know! We're gonna have so much fun!
抱歉 我迟到了 午餐持续的太久了
Oh, sorry I'm late; lunch ran a little long.
你找我 莫斯比?
You wanted to see me, Mosby?
差不多4个小时以前
Uh, yeah, like four hours ago.
不好意思  那段时间
Well, excuse me, for spending the last four hours
我在为你的大楼设计画图
drawing designs for your building.
这只不过是张鸡尾酒会餐巾纸
This is a cocktail napkin.
而且上面写满了脏话
Covered in profanity.
听着  汉默
Look, Hammond, um,
实在不知道该怎么跟你说
there's no easy way to say this, so...
我们为什么不到你的办公室去
why don't we just, um, step into your office.
# Happy birthday to you #
小子　真有你的 忽悠了我
- # Happy birthday to you # - Oh, you had me. You so had me.
# Happy birthday, dear Hammond #
# Happy birthday to you #
就这样  你没炒掉他
So, you didn't fire him?
我不能在一个人的生日开除他 所以人都会讨厌我
I can't fire a guy on his birthday. Everyone would hate me.
另外 他们给我戴上了派对帽 我的威严也打折了
Besides, they put a party hat on me. My authority was compromised.
马修坐下来
Oh, hey, Marshall. Have a seat.
我知道你有多喜欢凳子
I know how much you love stools.
谢谢 凳子能 矫正你的坐姿
Thanks. Yeah, stools are better for your posture.
我要送你玫瑰
And, uh... I... got you a rose.
谢谢 很浪漫
Thank you. That's so sweet.
你们很浪漫
You guys are being... so sweet.
猜猜我得到了什么 新的飞镖
Hey, guys. Guess what I got. A new dart.
新的飞镖...
Oh, wow, a new dart.
新的飞镖很棒
Hey, that new dart is great.
我不知道你这么喜欢新飞镖
I did not know you were such a fan of new dart, Barney.
是的  罗宾 我喜欢新飞镖
Oh, yes, Robin, I just love new dart.
裸体艺术 (新飞镖的同音)
Nude art.
-裸体艺术 -裸体艺术
- Nude art. - Nude art.
这么说来你们发现那幅画了
Okay, all right, so what, you guys found the painting, huh?
我知道这天迟早会到来
I knew this day would come.
你怎么会知道的
How did you know that?
因为我没有把它藏好
Because I didn't hide it very well.
这幅画的故事要从大学开始说起
So the story on the painting is that, back in college,
莉莉想为她的艺术课 画一幅裸体画
Lily wanted to do a nude study for her art class.
马修不赞成这主意
Marshall wasn't so into the idea.
我只是不要某个男的
Well, I just... don't think that some dude
脱下裤子为你摆造型
should drop trou just to pose for you.
这只是为了学业 而且我找的是那个怪怪的学弟亨特
It's for class, and it's just that weird kid Hunter from my freshman hall.
就是那个留了撮山羊胡 喜欢玩飞盘的家伙
The frisbee dude with the soul patch?
他在学校里炙手可热的
He's like the hottest guy in school!
不  他不过比较强壮
No, he's actually a little husky...
拥抱他的感觉一定很好
Oh, he's just huggable!
而且这人令人费解
And complicated...
还有点古怪
and a little bit of a jerk.
但这种古怪正好是 你认为能改变的程度
Just enough so you think maybe you can change him.
好的  不提了
Okay, just forget it.
说我守旧  好了
Call me old-fashioned,
我只是认为你 只能看我一个人的裸体
I just think that I'm the only guy you should see naked.
那好　那你o我画
Well, then you'll have to do it.
开玩笑  要是有人看到?
Are you kidding me? What if somebody sees it?
我们都不是高中生了
We're not in high school anymore.
人们不会为了裸体模特而取笑你的
People don't make fun of you for posing nude for a painting.
我们都是成年了
We're adults now.
我们看到你整个屁股
We totally saw your butt.
这幅画o了我太多痛苦
This painting has caused too much grief already.
我马上毁了它
I'm destroying it right now.
不要 怎么了
Oh, no, what's the matter, Marshall?
放在哪了
Where is it?
如果你猜下面三个谜语我就告诉你
I'll tell you where it is if you'll answer these riddles three.
你挂在了酒吧 是不是?
You hung it up in the bar, didn't you?
为什么你破坏我的谜语
Yo, why you gotta ruin my riddles?
野外旅行
Field trip!
错 有人把你的画 挂在了酒吧后面
Oh, no. Someone put your painting up behind the bar.
经典
Classic!
经典的恶作剧
What a memorable prank.
马修 你要什么
Hey, Marshall. What'll you have?
我要什么  不知道 也许是啤酒
What'll I have? Um, I don't know, maybe a beer
和挂在酒吧后面的裸体画
and that nude painting of me hanging behind the bar!
抱歉 那幅画是酒吧的财产
Ooh, I'm sorry, that painting's property of the bar.
我知道巴尼给了你幅画
I know that Barney gave you that painting.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
不论他给你多少  我给你双倍
Whatever he's paying you, I'll pay you double.
不相信
I doubt it.
不论他给你多少 我将再多付你10块
Whatever he's paying you, I'll give you that plus ten bucks.
不相信
I doubt it.
你知道的 卡尔 你会失去一个老客户
All right, you know what, Carl, you just lost yourself a regular customer.
不相信
I doubt it.
这副画是我最惨痛的经历
This painting is the worst thing that's ever happened to me.
下一步我们把他放在哪 在他的法律学校
Okay, where should we put it up next? In his law school?
挂在公交车的侧面
Ooh on the side of a bus. Oh, oh!
做一个广告牌要多少钱
How much do billboards cost?
冷静 不着急 注意策略...
Easy, Scherbatsky. Finesse.
我有了一个5年展览计划
I've got a five-year rollout plan.
我会这幅画享誉整个城市
I'll have you know that painting's got commitments all over the city.
同时 在纽约之后...
Then, after New York...
一个我最怕的事实终于实现了
One of my worst fears has come true--
我刚看到马修 抓住裸体的自己
I just saw Marshall grabbing himself naked.
我得走了
Well, I gotta go.
无论你信不信  我得回办公室了
Believe it or not, I have to go back to the office.
我和你一起走
Oh, I'll go out with you.
再见了  伙计们
Bye, guys.
我希望你们不要取笑这幅画
You know, I wish everyone didn't have to make fun of that painting.
我们没取笑这幅画 我们只是取笑马修
Eh, we're not making fun of the painting, we're just making fun of Marshall.
这幅画确实是很不错的
The painting's actually really great.
- 真的? - 是的
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
谢谢了
Well, thank you.
再一次看到它  使我怀念裸体画
You know, seeing it again makes me miss painting nudes.
什么
What?
画我
Paint me.
什么
What?
画我
Paint me.
那是谁
Who's that?
谁在那里
Who's out there?
汉默 是你?
Hammond, is that you?
莫斯比
Mosby?
我和德拉泽 单独留在办公室里
Druthers and I were alone in the office.
如果我要解雇他
If I was gonna fire him,
这就是最好的时机了
this would be the best chance I'd ever have.
等下  泰德
Uh, look, just a second, Ted.
我真得和你谈谈
Uh, no, I, I really need to talk to you.
这有点难以启齿
Look, there's no easy way to say...
什么 你在干什么
What, what are you doing?
在干什么
What are you doing?
我正站在这里穿裤子
I'm standing here wearing pants.
你想在这里睡觉? 怎么了
Are you sleeping here? What's going on?
好的 是的
Okay, fine, yes.
没你的事
Not that it's any of your business
但是几周前我和我老婆 有了点小口角
but my wife had a little spat a few weeks ago,
我得一直睡在这直到她气消了
and I've been sleeping here until she cools off.
你说的没错  没我什么事
Okay, well, uh, you're right-- that is none of my business.
实在开不了口
Uh, look, there's no easy way to say this-- I...
我骗谁?
Who am I kidding?
她再也不会回心转意了
She's never gonna take me back.
没事的
It's okay.
你要对我说什么
What did you want to say to me?
生日快乐 兄弟
Happy birthday, buddy.
所以你一直住在办公室里?
So, you've been living at the office?
是的
Yes.
我是一个无家可归的建筑师
I'm an architect without a home.
你知道有多么的讽刺了吧
You see the tragic irony in that?
- 是的 知道了 - 因为我设计房子
- Yeah, I do. - 'Cause I design homes.
- 我知道了 - 但是我没有个家
- I see it. - But I don't have a home.
对我来说没什么可失去的了
Not lost on me at all.
但是我不懂的是 你为什么不去酒店
But I don't understand-- why don't you just go to a hotel?
你本可以睡在床上而不在这
You could be sleeping on a mattress instead of...
睡在我的建筑设计图
what appears to be torn-up drawings of my building.
我怎么可以去旅馆
Why would I go to a hotel, when any second,
在这里她随时都有可能 打电话给我叫我回家
she's going to call and tell me to come home.
她是一个十分特别的女人
She's a very special lady, Ted.
她十分男性化
She's quite... mannish.
她给我一切我需要的
She gives me what I need.
你明白吗
Do you understand that?
不  不明白
Uh, no, I don't.
如果你在野外迷路了
If you were lost in the wilderness,
她可以提供我所需要的
she can provide for me.
那是假设
Well, that's the dream.
十分高兴今晚你能来这
I'm glad you came here tonight, Ted.
我也是 汉默
Me too, Hammond.
- 叫我汉 就可以了 - 不 谢谢
- Call me Ham. - No, thanks.
- 汉哥 呢 - 不  叫汉哥很好
- Hammy D? - No, I think just Hammond.
因此 我猜你没有炒掉他
So, I'm guessing you didn't fire him.
就差那么一点
I was this close.
同时  莉莉一夜没睡好
Meanwhile, Lily had been up all night
进退两难
in the grips of a dilemma.
- 亲爱的 你醒了? - 是
- Oh honey, you're awake? - I'm awake.
- 没事吧 - 没事
- Is everything okay? - Yeah.
我被一些事困扰着
I've kind of been wrestling with something.
如果我告诉你我有办法 付我们蜜月的费用
What if I told you I had a way to pay for our honeymoon?
宝贝 我们已经付了钱了
Baby, our honeymoon's already paid for.
我们去地下溶洞 (纽约州的一个旅游景点)
We're going to Howe Caverns.
但是如果我不想 在溶洞里度蜜月
Well yeah, but-- but what if we didn't want to spend our honeymoon in a cave?
它不仅仅是一个溶洞 也是一个迷宫
It's not just a cave, it's a whole labyrinth of caves.
这是一次地下冒险
It's an underground adventure.
那有一个洞 暗到伸手不见五指
There's a cave that's so dark that you don't even know you're in there.
我们将会经历一种 全新的不同的黑暗
I mean, we're going to experience a whole new kind of dark.
如果我发现一个办法 可以赚一点额外的钱
Well, what if I found a way to make a little extra money
那样我可以不在溶洞里度蜜月
so that we spend our honeymoon not in Howe Caverns,
而在苏格兰?
but in Scotland?
- 尼斯湖水怪 - 是的
- Loch Ness? - Yeah.
爱丁堡  高地  格拉斯哥
And you know, Edinburgh and the Highlands and Glasgow...
尼斯湖  尼斯湖水怪
Loch Ness. Nessy.
我也想探索这个令人着迷的水怪
Baby, I would love to search for the enchanted creature of the Emerald Loch,
但是 我们负担不起
but... we can't afford that.
也许我们可以
Maybe we can.
画我
Paint me.
不明白
Okay, I don't get this.
你一直在取笑那幅画
You've been making fun of that painting all this time
现在你想我画你
and now you want me to paint you?
我们知道我们可以拿他折磨马修 因为他有羞耻心
We knew we could torture Marshall because he has shame.
我没有
I do not.
在我身上原本长羞耻腺体的地方
In my body, where the shame gland should be,
长着第二个神奇腺
there's a second awesome gland.
真的
True story.
不是腺  我担心画
Yeah, that's not the gland I'm worried about painting.
好的
Yeah.
画裸体巴尼是一个挑战
A nude Barney is a challenge.
但我想你的天分 能使他成为不朽的杰作
But I think you're talented enough to immortalize this.
现在正是时候 我31岁了
Now is the time-- I'm 31.
我在我身体最佳的状态
I'm at the peak of my physical beauty.
如果我是一个女的 就过了这个时期很久了
If I were a woman, I'd have passed it long, long ago.
很久了
Long ago.
算了
Forget it.
我答应过马修 他是我唯一看过裸体的男人
I promised Marshall he was the only guy I would ever see naked.
我给你5000美圆
I'll give you $5,000.
我们去尼斯湖
We're going to Loch Ness!
好的
Yeah!
这个司机叽叽歪歪说个不停
That cabby would not shut up.
我们应该叫他唐僧
Yeah, we should call him a gabby.
我刚在想 你就说出来了
I think it, you say it.
谢谢你昨晚收留我 兄弟
Hey, uh... thanks for putting me up last night, buddy.
忘了那些
Give 'em hell.
早上好 伙计
Morning, team.
我又想了想
So, I have given it some thought,
我说我们再考虑一下圆柱
and I say we revisit columns.
天啊  不要了吧
Oh, God, not this again.
一个穿宽外袍的人刚刚到 送来一个羊皮纸
Ted, a man in a toga just arrived and delivered a parchment.
让我来看看
Let me read it:
这是从古希腊来的
Oh! It's from ancient Greece.
他们想要拿回他们的建筑专利
They want their basic architectural elements back.
- 天那 - 什么?
- Geez. - What?
你没听到我说的吗
You didn't hear me?
宽长袍  羊皮纸
Toga, parchment...
能到边上谈会?
Can I see you for one second?
现在我有麻烦了
Ooh, I'm in trouble now.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
你睡在我的沙发上 吃着我的麦片
You slept on my couch, you ate my cereal.
我给你拿了很多卫生纸
I tossed you more toilet paper.
我们是朋友
We are friends.
但这不会奇迹般 使你的烂创意变好
But that doesn't magically make your bad ideas good.
什么?我不敢相信
What? I don't believe this!
你穿我的衣服
You're, you're, you're wearing my clothes!
我女朋友的运动鞋
And my girlfriend's... sneakers--
你有一双奇怪的小脚
man, you have weirdly small feet.
我希望你不会 让我们工作上的分歧
Ted, I hope that you're not going to let our professional woes
影响到我们的友谊
interfere with our friendship,
因为我现在真的需要你
because I really kind of need you right now.
让我们开始
Okay, let's get this over with.
我不想让你在这打电话
Hey, hey! I don't want you phoning this in.
这幅画假以时日 可能会成为著名的艺术品
This painting could, someday, become a serious work of art.
上帝赐予你了惊人的天赋
I mean, you have been blessed with an amazing gift.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是说我自己...
I meant me.
我喜欢你那幅画里 体现出的气质
Now, I like how you captured Marshall's essence.
憨厚  天真 又带一点聪明
Goofy and unburdened, with wit.
但是我 我想要一些帝王气
But me, I want something more regal.
一种我的后代会瞻仰并说
Something my progeny could look at and say,
那矗立的巴尼・斯丁森
"There's stands Barnabus Stinson."
他智慧
He was wise...
并强壮
and strong.
我觉得你不必拿剑
I don't think your sword will fit.
双关,Barney意为很多妹子说他那玩意很大
我剑太多了
I get that a lot.
于是当莉莉开始画画
And so, as Lily began painting,
马修想着5000美圆
Marshall thought about the $5,000
和他的未婚妻会做什么来赚到它
and what his fiance was doing to earn it.
这不对
This isn't right.
完全不对
This isn't right at all.
他终于控制不住了
Finally, he could take it no more.
别动!
Hold still.
别动!!
- 别动!!! - 快点画
- Hold still! - Paint faster!
我想是时候了
Okay, I guess it's time.
脱下你的小裤裤
Drop your shorts.
好
Yeah.
等等
Wait, wait!
还没做好准备 我需要...
That wasn't enough buildup. I need...
在一个没有正义的世界 一个人
In a world without justice, one man--
- 脱吧 - 好
- Oh, just drop them! - All right.
不  这不对 我们说好了的
- No! No, this is not right! - We had a deal!
我要终止这个协议 巴尼出去...
Well, I'm going back on the deal. Barney, get out!
- 你... - 结束了
- You...! - It's over!
我不能让你受这些煎熬
Lily, I can't let you go through with this!
我找到一个我们可以待的城堡 但是还要再加200块
I found a castle we can stay in, but it's an extra two grand.
这不对
It's just not right!
那是美丽的地方而且那里还闹鬼
It's beautiful and they say it's haunted.
我不能让我爱的女人 为了钱出卖自己
I can't let the woman I love compromise her values for money!
我想我们可以 从他那多捞点钱
I totally think we can get some more money out of him.
我从不会让我的未婚妻
I'm never letting my fiance, ever...!
你还在着?
Oh, you're still here?
在你说任何事之前
Before you say anything,
我再o你5美圆
I'll give you an extra five grand.
好的
We accept.
你们这些人太好控制了
You people are so easy to control.
为我跳舞 木偶们  跳舞
Dance for me, puppets, dance.
那就是巴尼叔叔如何付了 莉莉和马修的蜜月费用
And that's how Uncle Barney paid for Lily and Marshall's honeymoon.
拜托 泰德 听着 我们为什么不回去
Come on, Ted, listen, why don't we get back
完成这个大楼的设计图
and finish drawing the plans for a building
一个在我看来 永远建不成的大楼
which, in my opinion, is never going to get built,
所以我建议我们 还是去喝两杯啤酒
so you and I can get out of here and grab a couple of beers.
不
No.
听着 汉默 这有点难以启齿
Look, Hammond, there's no easy way to say this but...
哪位是汉默・德拉泽?
Looking for Hammond Druthers.
在这  我就是汉默・德拉泽
Oh, that's me. I'm Hammond Druthers.
这是离婚协议书
These are divorce papers.
已经送达了
You've been served.
天啊
Oh, God.
她真的做了这些
She's really going through with this.
一切都结束了
So that's it. It's over.
这实在难以说出口...
There is no easy way to say this, but...
他给了我沃尔菲的遗体
She's giving me the remains of Wolfie?
我的狗死了?
My dog is dead?
天啊  我不敢相信
Oh, my God. I can't believe this.
她总是和它玩的太过火
She always played too rough with him.
相信我 实在难以启齿说这个...
Believe me, there is no easy way to say this--
祝你生日快乐 你们在开我玩笑?
- # Happy birthday to you... # - You've got to be kidding me!
你们不知道此时此刻 这对我意味着什么
Guys, you have no idea how much this means to me right now.
等等  他的生日是昨天
Wait, his birthday was yesterday!
没错  但是昨天我们 大部分在蒙特利尔开会
Yeah, but a bunch of us were up at the conference in Montreal,
- 因此 我们想... - 不要过生日了  不要了
- so we thought... - No! No birthday! No!
我要话要说 我现在就要说出来
I got something to say and I'm gonna get it out.
汉默 听我说 很抱歉你的狗死了
Hammond, listen to me. I am sorry that your dog died,
你的妻子和你离婚了
and that your wife is divorcing you and that...
你的生活支离破碎了 那些人错过了你的生日
your life is falling apart and that these guys missed your birthday.
这实在是难以启齿
And there is no easy way to say...
你在干什么  怎么了?
What are you doing? What's going on?
天啊
Oh, God...
拜托　你不会来这招吧
Oh, come on, you're not going to pull that, are you?
看  没错 现在倒下了
Oh! Look, yeah, right. Now we're falling onto the ground.
很好  但是你猜我会说什么
Well, nice try, but guess what?
你被解雇了
You're fired!
你被解雇了 明白了吗 听到我说了吗
You're fired-- you get it? You hear me?
你要走人了  你被解雇了
You're gone! You're fired!
站在我角度 我想我们都怀疑汉默
In my defense, I think we all suspected Hammond
可能是假装的
might have been faking.
救护人员对也认为他不会有事
On the plus side, the EMTs seem to think he's going to be just fine
大家都看到了 他们确实认为不是我引起他的心脏病的
and, as you saw, they did admit that I did not cause the heart attack,
尽管他们说的那么不情愿
even if they said it a bit begrudgingly.
但最糟糕的是
And there it was, rock bottom:
他们都讨厌我
They all hated me.
不过  正当一切似乎失去了
But just when all seemed lost,
同时我职业生涯中 最伟大的创意产生了
I had the greatest idea of my entire career.
星期五鸡尾酒 好主意  头
Margarita Fridays-- great idea, boss.
画好了
Okay, it's done.
我出去了 因此你可以来欣赏下
I'm gonna step out, so you can admire it.
非常感谢 莉莉
Thank you very much, Lily.
钱够了吗?
Marshall, do you have the money?
- 够了 - 我们马上走
- Yeah. - Let's get out of here!
那里光滑一片...你画的是玩具?
A smooth area?! You gave me the Ken doll?!
她忘了画小巴尼
She left out Little Barney.
巴尼二世
Barnacle Junior.
我的香蕉是...
My Barnana is...
其实是超级无敌香蕉
Barnito Supreme.